<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Blog: Via Codigo</title>
    <link>https://blog.viacodigo.com/en/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Blog: Via Codigo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Vía Código</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 18:40:24 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.viacodigo.com/en/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>DIGITAL RIGHTS WORKSHOP AND ONLINE GENDER VIOLENCE</title>
      <link>https://blog.viacodigo.com/en/2018/11/30/taller-derechos-digitales-y-violencia-de-genero-en-linea/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 18:40:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.viacodigo.com/en/2018/11/30/taller-derechos-digitales-y-violencia-de-genero-en-linea/</guid>
      <description>We invited the Hiperderechoteam to talk with the workshop participants about the digital rights and to conduct an experimental workshop on online gender violence. Denisse Albornoz, Research Director, tells us her experience.
 How was your experience with the Via Codigo boys? The experience was wonderful. I was very nervous before arriving to the workshop. I didn’t know the boy’s expectation, nor to what extent were they willing to have an openly discussion about digital rights and online harassment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inteview with Mentor Roberto </title>
      <link>https://blog.viacodigo.com/en/2018/11/20/mentor-entrevista-roberto/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 16:10:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.viacodigo.com/en/2018/11/20/mentor-entrevista-roberto/</guid>
      <description>The mentor programme of Via Codigo connects known programmers from all around the world with students of our project. Present the students with options that open them to the world of programming, and put them in contact with professionals that don’t judge them for their past, but seek to help them move forward.
Roberto, Digital Nomad, Philosopher/Fullstack Developer, someplace in the world How do you think Web programming can help young people from VC to change their lives?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mentor Interview:  Eric</title>
      <link>https://blog.viacodigo.com/en/2018/08/15/mentor-entrevista-eric/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 12:04:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.viacodigo.com/en/2018/08/15/mentor-entrevista-eric/</guid>
      <description>The Via Codigo mentorship program connects reknown developers around the world with our students. It presents to the students the opportunities thata ppear when joining the programming world and connects them with professionals that don&amp;rsquo;t judge them by their past, they just want to help them develop a new future.
Eric, Software Engineer, Backend Web Development and Data Engineer, New York How do you think Web Development can help the students ar VC to change their lifes?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mentor Interview: Gonçalo</title>
      <link>https://blog.viacodigo.com/en/2018/08/01/mentor-entrevista-gon%C3%A7alo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 11:45:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.viacodigo.com/en/2018/08/01/mentor-entrevista-gon%C3%A7alo/</guid>
      <description>The Via Codigo mentorship program connects reknown developers around the world with our students. It presents to the students the opportunities thata ppear when joining the programming world and connects them with professionals that don&amp;rsquo;t judge them by their past, they just want to help them develop a new future.
Gonçalo, Front-end Developer at BridgeU y Recurse Center alumnus, London How do you think Web Development can help the students ar VC to change their lifes?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VÍA CÓDIGO A CURRENT PROPOSAL	</title>
      <link>https://blog.viacodigo.com/en/2018/07/01/via-codigo-una-propuesta-actual/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 18:22:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.viacodigo.com/en/2018/07/01/via-codigo-una-propuesta-actual/</guid>
      <description>A revolutionary gesture is to always deny what is instead of what we wish there was. And it might seem that the productive core of heroic subjectivity would not be to deny what is in the name of &amp;ldquo;what should be&amp;rdquo; but rather in the name of what might be&amp;rdquo; 1. Elena Aldea
 Thanks to our passion for football and after having gained front-door access to the big leagues, we now return as World Cup competitors.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>